(Chill piano music)
No matter the distance, no matter how
years
turn, love takes flight, with a promise of
return. It circles the
world, it knows where to land,
still warm in the touch of a welcoming
hand.
Boomerang of love, a flight never lost,
through shadows and storms, it still makes
its
course. Each time it is cast, it will
rise far above, returning
again, the boomerang of
love.
(Chill piano music)
Return, oh boomerang, to hearts that are
warm, to the unloved, the
gentle, the kind in the storm. And above
all, return with the truth from above,
to restore what was given, return as
love. Boomerang of love, a flight never
lost, through shadows and storms, it
still makes its course. Each time it is
cast,
it will rise far above, returning
again, the boomerang of
love. Through the arc of the sky and the
breadth
of the earth, love finds the lost
and rekindles their worth. No force can
deter, no shadow can
stay, the path of love's promise will
find its own way. Boomerang of
love, a flight never lost, through
shadows and storms, it still makes its
course. Each time it is cast, it will
rise far above, returning
again, the boomerang of
love.
(Chill piano music)
Forever it circles, forever it flies,
beneath the sun, through unending
skies. Boomerang of
love, in its endless return,
the fire keeps glowing, the heart's ever
burn.
(Chill piano music)